<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>POLIW.AT</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on POLIW.AT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Omari, SC-LLC</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 11:38:49 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>She Breaking Glass Ceiling</title>
      <link>/2017/07/29/she-breaking-glass-ceiling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 11:38:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/29/she-breaking-glass-ceiling/</guid>
      <description> saturday 1139 am * boarding a train @noon*
this project is special I started she breaking glass ceiling last Fall. I made the hook of the track while walking from my dorm to the studio listening to a BADBADNOTGOOD track on repeat. I got the flow of it and wanted to fix the words, it took hours to get it to its final form here;
You&#39;ll need a lighter to hire her she aspire to conquer perspire till you retire she think in code on computer she walking you stalker she feeling you heeling at uni barely breaking even but breaking glass Ceiling she breaking glass ceiling  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grasshopper My Grasshopper</title>
      <link>/2017/07/29/grasshopper-my-grasshopper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 09:47:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/29/grasshopper-my-grasshopper/</guid>
      <description>Grasshopper my Grasshopper &amp;lt;verse1&amp;gt; I speak to you in total confidence in consequence in pool go go girl went postal in my post office be super nice cause most are lost most are lonely few are loud I am loud I am proud Im a prophet of my past predicated upon all my mistakes if I love jimminy cricket spitting to crickets my miss takes I spit to you my Grasshopper I need a mentor I need a guru I need a mentor I cannot take this I cannot fake this no more I cannot take this no more I cannot work her no more &amp;lt;b&amp;gt;hook&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt; wax on | wax off?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trapt In The Womb</title>
      <link>/2017/07/29/trapt-in-the-womb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 09:03:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/29/trapt-in-the-womb/</guid>
      <description>had 2 beers last night Currently working on a trap song with lyrics exploring the perspective of not being born yet, and not necessarily wanting to be born. Since you&amp;rsquo;re constrained to the reality of our politics, biology, and paradigms; such as religion, capitalism, etc.
I got the idea at my sister&amp;rsquo;s house, when I took an image of her sonogram and ran it through a [max msp]() patch that converted the image data to MIDI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Look Out The Window</title>
      <link>/2017/07/29/look-out-the-window/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 08:54:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/29/look-out-the-window/</guid>
      <description>Look out the Window
Fantasy task list: Go to this document when needing a title for a track
On caltrain and I have to shit so bad. I have 40 minutes until I hit San Hoe.
Gossip:
Lisa currently won&amp;rsquo;t talk to her dad because he bought a tesla She is also having some sort of relations with a prisoner where she volunteers
Saturday 106 pm
Amtrak was two hours late.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Im Sitting On</title>
      <link>/2017/07/29/what-im-sitting-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 01:11:27 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/29/what-im-sitting-on/</guid>
      <description>300 gigs of my own personal audio recordings. Saturday 116 AM
The biggest treasure of my life is my recordings. I collect audio every day. Normal slice of life things. I constantly record people without them knowing. I call it guerilla audio, and I&amp;rsquo;m not going to stop. You can tell me it&amp;rsquo;s immoral, illegal, douchie, lock me up, kick my ass, and I still won&amp;rsquo;t stop. Strong words have been tossed between friends and family, and every once in a while someone tries to speak against it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Center Of Github</title>
      <link>/2017/07/28/the-center-of-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 23:17:06 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/28/the-center-of-github/</guid>
      <description>the center of github
I have a romantic thought. What’s at the center of Github? I imagine a room where someone makes beats as a 9-5. These beats help fuel the rest of the programming community. This person makes an instrumental track for each git command. Each track has it’s stems available on github.
My day job right now is web development. I am a primarily self taught programmer. I haven’t gone beyond doodling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I, your therapist at wits end</title>
      <link>/2017/07/28/i-your-therapist-at-wits-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 23:00:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/28/i-your-therapist-at-wits-end/</guid>
      <description>Friday 533 PM | OnCalTrain | JULY 28 2017 | #####I your therapist at wits end
Had 1 beer @ [jack&amp;rsquo;s]() house and we livestreamed the Sims 3 on Twitch as prep for our play. Just wanted to report on an occurrence that happened a couple months ago. After my last breakup, I went a little off the rails. No, not talking ruby, I maintained a healthy ecosystem of smoke and drink each day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Model_parents</title>
      <link>/2017/07/28/model_parents/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:38:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/28/model_parents/</guid>
      <description>I always wished I grew up in a household like this. I wanted nothing more than a laptop since the age of 6, but didn&amp;rsquo;t get my hands on a computer until some extreme manipulation in seventh grade. I got a shitty Dell that would run World of Warcraft at 12 FPS in Ogrimmar or Dalaran. I was an incredibly annoying lock for a while but my real soul was ganking, dueling and general pvping as an undead rogue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pbjmaster_1</title>
      <link>/2017/07/28/pbjmaster_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 10:30:53 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/28/pbjmaster_1/</guid>
      <description>Friday 10:31 AM
Don&amp;rsquo;t start reading until you play this
A major client we have here has a major page down for their international (french site). I really had to shit and drink coffee so I wasn&amp;rsquo;t much help and now I should be working on fixing that, but am also consulting my buddy tyler on some flexbox use for a client of his.
Going to Michigan on Tuesday, so real quick notes, these things have to happen today -</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Help</title>
      <link>/2017/07/27/help/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 12:19:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/27/help/</guid>
      <description>Bounce hour
Every week at my work there&amp;rsquo;s an hour where you can share your projects / ideas over free coffee and snacks. I go for the free coffee and snacks.
I don&amp;rsquo;t have any new ideas but listening to all my unfinished beats.
// need to make more music
Yesterday I failed at making live loops because I didn&amp;rsquo;t have good old DJ Chad Mike hitting record for me. The more I program, write, solder, the worse I get at being a musician.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>somedays just to live is courage</title>
      <link>/2017/07/26/somedays-just-to-live-is-courage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 20:42:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/26/somedays-just-to-live-is-courage/</guid>
      <description>Wed 842 pm July 26 2017-06 I don&amp;rsquo;t have anything to type anymore. I&amp;rsquo;ve been sober for a full 7 days now, and I&amp;rsquo;m pissed. I am angry. I will use this anger to get shit done, like log work hours, work on music
[Todd] hooked me up big time at the fab lab, and I met Chris and Jordan. Chris Maddox printed the first versions of POLIWAT for me and I&amp;rsquo;m super amped on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The year I was 25</title>
      <link>/2017/07/25/help1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/25/help1/</guid>
      <description>I dream in POLIWAT First off some sound
I have been completely sober for 5 days Tuesday 952 PM
At Diridon in San Jose. Hopefully the 17 bus comes and I&amp;rsquo;ll get to my place in Santa Cruz before midnight. My laptop charging porter burned out while on the train so this is the last charge until I repair it. I found a shop in San Jose that has a new pot I can install myself for 40 bucks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>